

CONTACT

(+48) 600 214 855

mariusz.majdak@onet.pl

Gdańsk

linkedin.com/in/mariuszmajdak github.com/mmajdak

SKILLS

Currently developing:

Jupyter Notebook PyCharm

Postgres SQL

Scikit learn

Visual Studio Code

Pandas

NumPy

Matplotlip

Git Bash

GitHub

Scrum

Python

SQL

Machine Learning
Google Colaboratory

Deep Learning

TanaarElaw

TensorFlow

MARIUSZ MAJDAK

Junior Data Scientist

PERSONAL PROFIL

For the last few years, I have worked in the logistics industry. However, being aware of my analytical skills, I decided to educate myself and learn about the methods of data analysis in IT. In the past, I studied at the University's Faculty of Economic Sciences, so I can analyze, process and interpret data. I would like to develop in my further professional career as the Junior Data Scientist.

EDUCATION

August 2021 - April 2022 - Data Science

infoShare Academy - Gdańsk - Number of hours on the course 445h

Tools/libraries: Postgres SQL, Git Bash, GitHub, Visual Studio Code, PyCharm, Jupy-ter
Notebook, Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, TensorFlow, OpenCV, Google Colaboratory

Technologies/methodologies: Python, SQL, Scrum, Tableu

Deep Learning project

Creating an application that uses the object-in-image detector (Yolov4) to recognize photos from microscope. The subject of interest was to find a blood cells for infected with malaria.

Machine Learning project

Development of an application that could be used by wine distributors to search for a new wines for their collection. The application took parameters (e.g. alcohol concentration, sulphates, pH) and made predictions that classified the wine as good or bad wines.

Python project

Kickstarter, that is the analysis of projects with crowdfunding funding. We created an application that showed which projects were successful in each country and calculated the probability (based on several factors) of what chances of success your project would have.

SQL project

Election 2016, that is the analysis of the US presidential elections. In the project gro-up, using the available data, we investigated how demographic factors determine who people vote for.

Novembaer 2010 - July 2011 - Certificate English Entry 3

Thurrock Adult Community College

Obtober 2003 - June 2008 - Management and Marketing

University of Warmia and Mazury Master of Management and Marketing

CONTACT

(+48) 600 214 855 mariusz.majdak@onet.pl Gdańsk

linkedin.com/in/mariuszmajdak github.com/mmajdak

LANGUAGES

English - B2 German - A2 Russian - A2 Italian - A1

HOBBY

Football: Ekstraklasa oraz 1 Liga Ski Jumping Formula 1

MARIUSZ MAJDAK

Junior Data Scientist

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2020 - Currently - Logistics Manager

Hegelmann/Express Heroes - Gdańsk

- Good knowledge of ERP Abona program
- · Negotiating freight rates with forwarders and carriers

March 2020 - April 2020 - Logistics Manager

DD Solutions - Sopot

- · Managing the logistics department and cooperation with shipping companies
- · Creation monthly cost statements
- Dealing with HR matters for drivers

September 2018 - December 2019 - International forwarder

VGL Group - Gdynia

- Cooperation with carriers and fleet management
- · Debt collection, issuing orders and invoices

March 2016 - August 2018 - International forwarder

AutoInwest - Gdańsk

- Service of transport exchanges and negotiations regarding freight rates
- Cooperation with carriers and managing a group of drivers

October 2014 - December 2015 - Logistics specialist

Trans-Form Sp. z o.o., Sp. k. - Sopot

- · Assessment of the execution of the order and contact with clients
- Company database administration

May 2013 - September 2014 - Mobile financial advisor

S4 Strefa kredytów/Sales Group - Gdańsk

- · Acquiring new customers and business meetings with them
- Cooperation with banks, participation in their training, getting to know them new offers

November 2009 - March 2013 - Warehouse worker

DHL Exel - West Thurrock - Wielka Brytania

- Completing orders according to orders
- Standard warehouse works

September 2008 - August 2009 - Administrative worker

Urząd Miejski w Lidzbarku Warmińskim - Lidzbark Warmiński

- · Work at the Faculty of Geodesy and Real Estate Management
- · Preparation of lease agreements for municipal land
- Assistance in organizing the sale of municipal land through auctions

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application in this document to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment processes under the Personal Data Protection Act (Journal of Laws of 2018, item 1000) and in accordance with the Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).